<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<myinfo>
		 <thefiturl>Explore where you belong.</thefiturl>
		 <thesearchurl>Search our careers.</thesearchurl>
		 
		 	 <head1>
		Senior Developer
		 </head1>	
		 
		 <pagetext1>
		 Working independently in a variety of technical environments, our Senior Developers provide high-level expertise in analysis, design and development, and application modification/enhancement. Their expertise assists Lead Developers in setting standards and best practices, and helps guide other team members. Integral to this role is proficiency in a broad range of related technologies, because these multitalented professionals often find themselves working on very large and/or complex assignments. Their skill sets include knowledge of JEE development, including JMS, JSP with struts, EJBs and WebServices (BEA WebLogic preferred), XML, SOAP and JDBC API. They are also familiar with Oracle databases and basic UNIX system administration tasks and tools.
		 </pagetext1>
		 
		 <head2>Customer Accounting/Collections Specialist</head2>

<urlsrch>
	<href>https://washingtonpostmedia.com/careers/?category_name=searchopening</href>
	<txt>search opportunities.</txt>
</urlsrch>

<urlintro>
	<href>https://washingtonpostmedia.com</href>
	<txt>our careers</txt>
</urlintro>
 
		 	 <pagetext2>
		 Our talented accounting experts work on projects ranging from contracts and new accounts to credit and collections, to billing, customer service and cash processing. They have a solid understanding of revenue accounting and our business processes, as well as various receivable systems and functionality (both SAP and DSI). The keys to performing well in this area include the ability to see the big picture and assist management in defining requirements, to interpret business processes and requirements to IT partners, and to act as a liaison and resource for our Marketing department.
		 </pagetext2>	
		 
		  <head3>Business Development</head3>
 
		 	 <pagetext3>
		 Savvy, motivated and hard-working -- that just begins to describe our Business Development experts. Some are tasked with seeking out employers within their territory to identify which of our products can help them meet their staffing needs. Others develop similar relationships that help us accomplish a variety of other vital activities. Essential to this role are sales ability and persuasiveness, tenacity and persistence, a client focus, strong managerial skills and a sense of creativity. Consultative sales techniques enable these professionals to build partnerships, sell online and print recruitment advertising and resolve any customer issues. Working at their best, they aim to meet and exceed quarterly revenue goals. Relevant experience, including knowledge of Salesforce.com and SAP, helps them thrive in this role.
		 </pagetext3>
		 
		 
		  <head4>Utility Worker</head4>
 
		 	 <pagetext4>
		 Maintaining the highest levels of efficiency and cleanliness in our production department is imperative to it's success. A large part of that responsibility is handled by our Utility Workers. They keep our floors clear of paper, ink and debris -- and perform many other general cleaning duties that are integral to our daily operations. They also maintain the supply of newsprint to the presses, work on a baling machine, clean presses inside and out, wash walls, mop reel room floors and handle ink for presses. Excellent communications skills are essential to this significant role because these employees interact with diverse workgroups, and must know how to stay safe in an ever-changing environment. Highly motivated self-starters with an excellent work record will make a great match with this significant role.
		 </pagetext4>	
		 
		  <head5>Copy Aide</head5>
 
		 	 <pagetext5>
		 Individuals with a talent for multitasking and an aptitude for taking on numerous responsibilities are an ideal fit for this entry-level position. In fact, our Copy Aides get to see our operations from a unique perspective as they deliver newspapers to our Newsroom, answer and direct calls, and handle everything from photocopying to filing, sorting and distributing mail and packages. Because these tasks are an essential part of our daily workflow, they require strong data entry skills, plus the ability to communicate well with others. Qualified applicants are enrolled at least part-time in an accredited college, university or graduate or professional school program. Detail-oriented self-starters can be very successful in this role.
		 </pagetext5>	
		 
		 
		   <head6>Software Engineer</head6>
 
		 	 <pagetext6>
		 Strong troubleshooting and communication skills are two of the most essential qualities our experts share in this position. Their work puts them in close contact with editorial staff members in order to develop and implement creative solutions that provide users with an excellent online experience. An affinity for journalism can make Web developers an ideal match for this position if they can also design and code our website applications and tools. Experience in leading a team, overcoming challenges, resolving customer issues and providing innovative recommendations are all part of what it takes for individuals to succeed in this career field.
		 </pagetext6>	
		 
		 
		    <head7>Product Manager</head7>
 
		 	 <pagetext7>
		Managers in this area are skilled at developing and launching Web products, overseeing the consumer experience and guiding the strategic direction of some of our most-visited sections, from employment to real estate and property management. These high-profile areas demand professionals who can make content meaningful to its audience, work in collaboration with various stakeholders and help develop innovative online avenues that will build our business and move it forward. Product development or product management experience, a background in product testing and exceptional business communications skills are essential.
		 </pagetext7>	
		 
		 
		    <head8>National Sales Planner</head8>
 
		 	 <pagetext8>
		Advertising is a major component of all organizations that make up Washington Post Media, so we consider our Sales Planners integral to our success. Working on our Advertising Sales team provides access to multiple aspects of sales as well as creative and client services in a medium that's always evolving. It's also a great place to start growing a career with the company. In this role, individuals perform a variety of tasks, from helping to complete and edit requests for proposals to preparing for sales calls, to researching and implementing marketing strategy and planning. This job demands a highly motivated, organized team player with a flexible attitude and the desire to work in a fast-paced environment.
		 </pagetext8>		
		 
		 
		 <head9>Manager, Editorial Tools & Projects</head9>
 
		 	 <pagetext9>
Looking to play a key role? As the manager of the Editorial Tools team, you'll take the lead in the development and maintenance of tools and databases used by the editorial team. You'll also be essential to the team's ability to launch new content features on the site, in coordination with the technology and business development departments. If you've got the skills it takes to implement and manage a project plan, along with related experience and strong interpersonal, writing and editing skills, this opportunity could be the one that helps you to take your career to the next level.
		 </pagetext9>
		 
		 	 <head10>Producer</head10>
 
		 	 <pagetext10>
		From breaking news to jobs, cars and real estate, to local arts and entertainment, when there's news to be shared, it's up to our Producers to find it, put a story together and get it online. The strengths needed for this role include the ability to easily assess something and state an opinion about it, a knack for handling multiple responsibilities in a fast-paced environment, and editorial and Web savvy. Journalism experience and a related degree are required, along with a creative mind, an independent spirit and excellent communication skills.
		 </pagetext10>	
		 
		 
		 <head11>Website Editor</head11>
 
		 	 <pagetext11>
		In today's online, highly interactive environment, technology has become much more than developing backend information to make a program work. It's a user experience. So our technology area includes editorial experts who can reach an audience -- not only to make them think, but to make them act. To that end, our Website Editors oversee all aspects of editing and production of expressnightout.com. They work with our publisher to define and meet the sites editorial mission, supervising a staff and collaborating with editors on the print edition team to maximize cross-promotion between the site and the paper. 
		 </pagetext11>	
		 
		  <head12>Assistant Managing Editor</head12>
 
		 	 <pagetext12>
		Covering the news can be very exciting --- and very demanding. It requires people with the talent and ability to move at a moment's notice, who are inspired by changing circumstances, and who want to get to the bottom of things in order to produce content of interest to readers. Individuals who hold the position of Assistant Managing Editor wear big shoes -- they oversee Express news coverage, and assign and direct that coverage, performing as the newsroom supervisor in the editor's absence. This role also advises the editor on newsroom operations, longer-term editorial projects and any staffing challenges.
		 </pagetext12>	
		
		 
		
		 
		  <head13>Account Manager</head13>
 
		 	 <pagetext13>
		The work we do involves identifying and qualifying prospects, then developing proposals to sell them on an idea. Our Account Managers handle this with great skill, making sales calls and presenting advertising plans and marketing research to clients. And this is just the starting point for developing and maintaining internal and external relationships. This role continues with the responsibility of selling across local and national industries and territories in a channel sales environment. The idea is ultimately to generate creative ideas that will help develop our business, including special sections, directories and special pages.
		 </pagetext13>	
		 
		 
	  <head14>Production Supervisor</head14>
 
		 	 <pagetext14>
		Meeting both editorial and sales requirements can be challenging. But that's just what our Production Supervisors do on a daily basis. They coordinate our daily flat plans, produce dummy pages and deadline lists for the editorial staff and ship completed pages to News IT. The Production Supervisor must also be prepared to coordinate any late ad moves with the appropriate departments. And the day isn't finished until all pages have been proofed. Their preflight activities help us ensure that any technical problems or space conflicts are corrected and our operations continue to run smoothly.
		 </pagetext14>	
		 
		 
		  <head15>Copy Chief</head15>
 
		 	 <pagetext15>
		Accuracy, consistency and the overall quality of our issues are vital to our business and reputation as one of the nation's leading newspapers. Lucky for us, we have a Copy Chief whose talent excels in those areas. But that's only part of the job. The Copy Chief also tracks our page flows for all daily, weekly and monthly Express sections. In fact, this position is our last line of defense against copy errors, including anything that might be regarded by readers as being in bad taste. This essential individual must also be prepared to keep the editor apprised of any recurring workflow or editing problems so that Express always makes for good reading.
		 </pagetext15>	
		 
		 
		   <head16>Graphic Designer (Web)</head16>
 
		 	 <pagetext16>
		When you're in the business of reporting the news, your work environment must be kept continually up-to-date. That's why, each week, our Graphic Designers focus on ensuring the content on our website is current. If it's not, they make whatever changes are needed, and redesign any areas of the site that need updating. By staying aware of the latest Web programming techniques they easily accomplish this task and many others. These talented individuals have a Web and graphic design background, and often join us straight out of school. It's a great position for those who want to share ideas, join a great company in a junior position and grow a full career. Bilingual ability is a must.
		 </pagetext16>	
		 
		 
		 	   <head17>Accounting Administrator</head17>
 
		 	 <pagetext17>
		Every day, our Accounting Administrators apply their expertise to keeping track of incoming and outgoing payments. Their watchful eyes are focused on managing all A/R activities, including invoicing and assisting clients with any issues, plus they handle collections and coordinate client accounts with our sales reps. Their ability to work closely with our advertising group is an essential asset for this role. The ideal person for this position has excellent administrative and bilingual communications skills. With these diverse talents, they are well-equipped to enter data for display ads and provide excellent customer service.
		 </pagetext17>	
		 
		 
		   <head18>Sales Representative</head18>
 
		 	 <pagetext18>
		When the phone rings, it's up to our Sales Reps to receive the call and sell our internal clients some ad space. Making cold calls to drum up new business is another of their strong points. In this vital position, these professionals take various classified and display ad requests -- including ads for employment or services, and for apartments, rentals or homes. Excellent customer service and organizational skills are a must, as these bilingual Sales Reps may find themselves writing or placing up to 100 ads in Spanish and English a week. One things for sure -- with this job you'll always be busy.  
		 </pagetext18>	
		 
		 
		 	   <head19>Graphic Designer (Advertising)</head19>
 
		 	 <pagetext19>
Our Graphic Designers put their creative talents to work producing anywhere from 20 to 30 new print ads daily. After receiving the ad specs and other details from our Sales Reps, they use Oracle to combine everything together according to client requests and their own unique artistic point of view. That means they're always able to put their own imprint on their work -- plus they get the opportunity to edit or redesign ads that were previously produced by an agency. Excelling in this role relies on the ability to take initiative on projects and work in a detail-oriented, fast-paced yet organized environment. Bilingual ability is a must when performing minor translation of ads received in English. 
		 </pagetext19>	
		 
		 
		 
		  <head20>Jr. Editorial Staff</head20>
 
		 	 <pagetext20>
What's happening in the local area? Whatever it is, it's up to our Jr. Editorial Staff members to report it. Each week, they meet with the managing editor to offer ideas of what news stories they want to cover. Whether it's sports, cultural events, regular news or something that could have a national or international impact, they'll follow a lead to make sure the story's told. To make it all happen, they go out into the field to interview people, acquire information from the wire services and develop all of that into a compelling story. That's where their editorial and writing background, proficiency in Spanish and strong English communications skills really come into play.  
		 </pagetext20>	
		 
		 
		 
		 
		 
		 	 
		 		 
    		 
    
	
	
	
	</myinfo>